http://www.traceminerals.com/privacy-policy

america's #1 Selling Trace mineral, Liquid Magnesium, ANd Sport Electrolyte Brand‡BUY NOWProductsNewApple Cider Vinegar GummiesLiquid Immunity+Immunity GummiesElderberry Immunity PowderElectrolyte Stamina Power Pak + ImmunityShop AllMineralsMagnesiumConcenTrace®Colloidal SilverIonic SinglesShop AllChildren'sKids MultiChildren's Chewable ProbioticComplete Children's ChewableConcenTrace® Kids Trace Mineral DropsFeed My BrainTMSkincareBentonite ClayMagnesium GelMagnesium LotionPure Magnesium FlakesPure Magnesium OilShop AllFitnessTMSPORT Pre WorkoutPost WorkoutHydrationProteinShop AllCondition SpecificImmunityKeto EnergyStress & SleepDigestiveLongevityGluten FreeVegan VegetarianPopularPower PakEffervescent TabletsGummiesDr. Starkey LineMagnesiumElectrolytesSee our full catalogWellnessMultivitaminsSuperfoodsHeart HealthShop AllApple Cider Vinegar GummiesLEARN MORELiquid Immunity+LEARN MOREBulk/INternationalPrivate LabelAMERICA'S #1 SELLING TRACE MINERAL, LIQUID MAGNESIUM, AND SPORT ELECTROLYTE BRAND‡New ProductsElderberry + Ionic ZincVitamin C + ZincSugar Free PowerPakHydration I.V. Electrolyte Drink PaksKeto Electrolyte PowderSee AllMineralsMagnesiumConcenTrace®Ionic SinglesSee AllChildrensKids MultiChildren's Chewable ProbioticComplete Children's ChewableConcentrace® Kids Trace Mineral DropsFeed My BrainSee AllTm SkincareBentonite ClayMagnesium GelMagnesium LotionPure Magnesium FlakesPure Magnesium OilSee AllFitnessTMSPORTPre WorkoutPost WorkoutHydrationProteinLiquid Zinc Magnesium AspartateSee AllCondition SpecificImmunityKetoEnergyStress & SleepDigestiveLongevityGluten FreeVeganVegetarienPopularPower PakEffervescent TabletsGummiesDr. Starkey LineMagnesiumElectrolytesWellnessMultivitaminsSuperfoodsHeart HealthSee Our Full CatalogInternationalPrivate LabelPrivacy PolicyThis policy describes the ways we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. You accept this policy by using our website or by purchasing our product. We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post itHow we collect information about youWhen you visit TraceMinerals.com, we collect your IP address and standard web log information,If you join our email list, we collect the following types of information:Contact information - your name and email address.We may also require that you provide additional information to verify your identity or address.How we use the personal information we collectOur primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. We may use your personal information to:Provide the services and customer support you requestSend notices about our services and troubleshoot problemsCustomize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our websiteHow we use cookiesWhen you access our website, we may place small data "cookies" on your computer.We send a "session cookie" to your computer when you log in to your account. This type of cookie helps us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages on our site during the same session. Once you log out or close your browser, this cookie expires and no longer has any effect.How we protect and store personal informationThroughout this policy, we use the term "personal information" to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We store and process your personal information on our computers in the US, and we protect it by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable US federal and state regulations. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption; we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files; and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities.How you can contact us about privacy questionsIf you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact us by writing to us at: info@traceminerals.com
